

285 Old Westport Road North Dartmouth, MA 02747

Artist. Designer. Educator.

I am a student artist pursuing a career in art education who values the hard work and interpersonal skills required to lead a classroom in advanced artistic activities. I plan to collaborate with fellow artists and the community to generate meaningful experiences through art.

Education: GPA: 3.92

University of Massachusetts Dartmouth, Class of 2020 BFA in Art Education with a Concentration in Graphic Design Chancellor's List (2016-Present) Honors Student

Employment:

New England Yachad	Staff Member (2019) Intern (2018) Yachad is a non-profit organization which works toward engagement and inclusion services for people with disabilities. With New England Yachad, I teach art classes, design informational and branding materials, complete various administrative tasks, and most importantly, engage with adults with a variety of disabilities.
America Reads	Tutor (2017-2018) As an America Reads tutor at Carney Academy, I assisted a first grade classroom with learning, classroom behavior, and interpersonal skills.
Bertucci's	Carry-Out Associate (2017) As a carry-out associate at a restaurant, I answered phones, packed orders, and engaged with customers to give them the best take-out dining experience possible.
Marshall's	Associate (2015-2017) As an employee in the Men's and Kid's departments, I helped customers, learned organizational skills, and multitasked between cleaning, returns, checkout, and pushing items from the back room.

Specialized Skills:

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, HTML, CSS, Traditional Painting, Digital Painting, Drawing, Teaching, Curriculum Design, Research, Communication and Writing.

Leadership Activities:

Honors Council UMass Dartmouth	Creative Specialist and
	Paint Night Leader (2018-
	Present)
	Secretary (2016-2018)
Yearbook	Cover Artist & Artistic
	Editor (2015-2016)
Junior Cotillion Mural	Designer and Co-Leader
	(2015)

Awards:

Jennifer W. Mulnix University Honors Program Service Award (2019) Chancellor Merit Scholarship (2016-Present) Robello Art Scholarship (2016) Shirley Lavoie Memorial Art Scholarship of Chelmsford Art Society (2016) AP Scholar with Distinction (2016)